{
    "subject": "resource/Shade_Empire",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Kuopio",
    "human_readable": "Shade Empire is from Kuopio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.973879873752594,
            "question": "Is Shade Empire located in Kuopio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.602994978427887,
            "question": "Where is Shade Empire from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5908300876617432,
            "question": "Shade Empire hails from which place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5623919367790222,
            "question": "Where did Shade Empire come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5260763764381409,
            "question": "From which location does Shade Empire originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39017337560653687,
            "question": "Shade Empire's origin is...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.311576247215271,
            "question": "What city is associated with Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.295549213886261,
            "question": "What is the origin city of Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23437868058681488,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15766966342926025,
            "question": "What city can be considered Shade Empire's home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shade Empire is from Kuopio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4394_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the birthplace of Shade Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4394_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin city of Shade Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4394_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is associated with Shade Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4394_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4394_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can see that there are multiple mentions of \"Shade Empire\" and its origins. Here's my evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is:\n\"Shade Empire is from Kuopio.\"\n\nAfter analyzing the documents, I found at least 5 instances where Shade Empire's origin is mentioned as Kuopio, Finland (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4394/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4394/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4394/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt, and twice with similar information as file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4394/re-ranker-msmarco/105.txt).\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Shade Empire is from Kuopio, Finland. Therefore, the triple \"Shade Empire is from Kuopio\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}